<SheffieldHYS id="17668">
<BaseURL><entry>http://www.sheffieldhelpyourself.org.uk/full_search_new.asp?group=17668</entry>
</BaseURL>
<HYSID><entry>17668</entry>
</HYSID>
<OrgName><entry>DRIVING STANDARDS AGENCY</entry>
</OrgName>
<Desc><entry>An automated service.  An information and booking service for driving tests, including motorcycles and lorries.  Provides information about driving theory tests, driving tests and local test centres.  Aims to contribute to the public service agreement objective to achieve a 40% reduction in riders and drivers killed or seriously injured in road accidents by continuing to promote road safety by influencing driver and rider behaviour.  Sets standards for pre-driver education, driver trainers, educating drivers, supervising trainers and carrying out theory and practical driving/riding tests.  The Driving Standards Agency is an Executive Agency of the Department for Transport which is responsible for setting standards and conducting theory (where applicable) and practical driving tests for many different types of vehicle.  Also responsible for the statutory regulation of driving instructors and trainers and the promotion of voluntary registers and non-statutory activities to improve driving standards.  Written test complaints/enquiries should be sent to DSA, Theory Tests, PO Box 381, Salford, M50 3W.</entry>
</Desc>
<Website><entry>http://www.direct.gov.uk/motoring</entry>
</Website>
<Address><entry>DSA PO Box 280</entry>
<entry>Newcastle-upon-Tyne</entry>
<entry>Tyne &amp; Wear</entry>
<entry>NE1 6PB</entry>
</Address>
<Telephone><entry>0300 200 1122</entry>
<entry>Telephone 1 Details:</entry>
<entry>low rate call</entry>
</Telephone>
<Fax><entry>0300 200 1155</entry>
<entry>Minicom:</entry>
<entry>0300 200 1144</entry>
</Fax>
<Email><entry>customer.services@dsa.gsi.gov.uk</entry>
</Email>
<ProviderServiceDetails><entry>Mon-Fri 8am-6pm (booking/enquiry office)</entry>
</ProviderServiceDetails>
<Provision><ProvisionPlace><entry>Sheffield (Middlewood Road) Driving Test Centre</entry>
<entry>508 Middlewood Road</entry>
<entry>Sheffield</entry>
<entry>South Yorkshire</entry>
<entry>S6 1TQ</entry>
</ProvisionPlace>
<ProvisionPlace><entry>Sheffield - Parkway</entry>
<entry>Unit 2</entry>
<entry>Acres Hill Business Park</entry>
<entry>Acres Hill Lane</entry>
<entry>Sheffield</entry>
<entry>South Yorkshire</entry>
<entry>S9 4LR</entry>
</ProvisionPlace>
<ProvisionPlace><entry>Sheffield LGV Driving Test Centre</entry>
<entry>Orgreave Way</entry>
<entry>Sheffield</entry>
<entry>South Yorkshire</entry>
<entry>S13 9LT</entry>
</ProvisionPlace>
</Provision>
<category><entry>TRANSPORT</entry>
</category>
</SheffieldHYS>
