<SheffieldHYS id="17761">
<BaseURL><entry>http://www.sheffieldhelpyourself.org.uk/full_search_new.asp?group=17761</entry>
</BaseURL>
<HYSID><entry>17761</entry>
</HYSID>
<OrgName><entry>EDGE CLIMBING CENTRE, THE</entry>
</OrgName>
<Desc><entry>Indoor climbing centre providing lead and top rope climbing for experienced and novice climbers.  Full range of climbing courses available for adults and young people starting from the basics and developing through a five stage process of basic skills and movement coaching.  Fully supervised climbing with qualified instructors.  Climbing equipment and refreshments are included.  Also runs a climbing club with continued development including climbing outdoors in the Peak District.  Children's courses start at 7 years and over (Rockstars) and for children aged 10 years and over (Edge Masters).  The junior "Introduction to Climbing Course" is an indoor course for young people aged 13-17 years.  The area's main centre for the new NICAS programme for young people, which rewards climbing achievements with the award of certificates to record progress.  Please see www.nicas.co.uk for full details.  Outdoor shop sells a full range of climbing equipment.</entry>
</Desc>
<Website><entry>http://www.sheffieldclimbing.com</entry>
</Website>
<Pubs><entry>Information brochure</entry>
</Pubs>
<Address><entry>Harland Works</entry>
<entry>John Street</entry>
<entry>Sheffield</entry>
<entry>South Yorkshire</entry>
<entry>S2 4QU</entry>
</Address>
<DisabledAccess><entry>Wheelchair Accessible;</entry>
</DisabledAccess>
<ContactName><entry>Phil Robins, Company Owner</entry>
</ContactName>
<Telephone><entry>0114 275 8899</entry>
</Telephone>
<Email><entry>info@sheffieldclimbing.com</entry>
</Email>
<ProviderServiceDetails><entry>Mon-Fri 10am-10.30pm, Sat &amp; Sun 10am-6pm (summer and Bank Holidays), Sat &amp; Sun 10am-8pm (winter), Thurs 4.30-6.30pm, Sat 9.30-11.30am &amp; 12noon-2pm (Rockstars, aged 7 years and over), Tues 4.30-6.30pm, Sun 10am-12noon (Edge Masters, aged 10 years and over), Fri 4-7pm (Friday Night Club, aged 14-17 years)</entry>
</ProviderServiceDetails>
<category><entry>CLIMBING AND MOUNTAINEERING</entry>
</category>
</SheffieldHYS>
