<SheffieldHYS id="18519">
<BaseURL><entry>http://www.sheffieldhelpyourself.org.uk/full_search_new.asp?group=18519</entry>
</BaseURL>
<HYSID><entry>18519</entry>
</HYSID>
<OrgName><entry>WILLOWBECK HEALTH CARE</entry>
</OrgName>
<AltName><entry>HOLYWELL COURT</entry>
</AltName>
<Desc><entry>A nursing home providing 24-hour care for younger adults between the ages of 18-65.  There are 5 individual units.  Ladybower and Carsington offer long or respite care to adults with complex physical disabilities which also include critical care needs.  Derwent, Howden and Rivelin care for adults with mental health problems whose behaviours may challenge the service.  Each unit's high staffing numbers reflects the assessed needs of the residents.  There are representatives from 3 branches of nursing: RMN, RGN and RNLD.  There is a full in-house activity team and 6 weekly visits by the chiropodist and weekly visits by the hairdresser.  The Home has full access to a dietitian and psychiatrist.  A GP provides a weekly clinic and can be contacted as an emergency out of hours.  Dietary intake on all the units can be closely monitored and specialised diets catered for on request.  All bedrooms are single en-suite and can be decorated to individual taste.  Personal possessions are welcomed.  Pets may be accommodated after discussion with the Manager.  This care home is registered and inspected by the Care Quality Commission (CQC), to make sure they provide a quality service.</entry>
</Desc>
<Langs><entry>Interpreters by arrangement</entry>
</Langs>
<Address><entry>95 Holywell Road</entry>
<entry>Sheffield</entry>
<entry>South Yorkshire</entry>
<entry>S4 8AR</entry>
</Address>
<DisabledAccess><entry>Wheelchair Accessible;</entry>
<entry>Wheelchair Accessible Toilet;</entry>
</DisabledAccess>
<ContactName><entry>Dawn Eden, Registered Manager/Rachel Lister</entry>
</ContactName>
<Telephone><entry>0114 261 7771</entry>
</Telephone>
<Fax><entry>0114 261 9779</entry>
</Fax>
<Email><entry>deden@exemplarhc.com</entry>
<entry>willowbeck@exemplarhc.com</entry>
</Email>
<ProviderServiceDetails><entry>Daily 9-5pm</entry>
</ProviderServiceDetails>
<category><entry>PRIVATE MEDICAL SERVICES</entry>
</category>
</SheffieldHYS>
