<SheffieldHYS id="19182">
<BaseURL><entry>http://www.sheffieldhelpyourself.org.uk/full_search_new.asp?group=19182</entry>
</BaseURL>
<HYSID><entry>19182</entry>
</HYSID>
<OrgName><entry>CARE QUALITY COMMISSION</entry>
</OrgName>
<AltName><entry>COMMISSION FOR SOCIAL CARE AND INSPECTION</entry>
</AltName>
<Desc><entry>The Care Quality Commission is the new health and social care regulator for England.  Looks at the joined up picture of health and social care.  Aims to ensure better care for everyone in hospital, in a care home and at home.  Responsible for inspecting and registering residential care homes in Sheffield for older people, young people, adults with learning disabilities or mental health problems, people with alcohol or drug problems, whether privately owned, local authority owned, run by a voluntary society or by a trust such as Sheffcare.  Regulates and inspects the Health Service.  Annual inspection reports are available on-line at www.csci.org.uk and at care homes on request.  Also registers domicilary care agencies and nurse agencies.  Covers Sheffield, Barnsley, Rotherham and Doncaster.  Has a range of legal powers and duties which include: registering providers of health care and social care; monitoring how providers comply with the standards; using enforcement powers; acting to protect patients whose rights are restricted; promoting improvement in services; carrying out special reviews, seeking the views of people who use services; telling people about the quality of their local care services.</entry>
</Desc>
<Website><entry>http://www.cqc.org.uk</entry>
</Website>
<Address><entry>CQC North East</entry>
<entry>Citygate</entry>
<entry>Gallowgate</entry>
<entry>Newcastle-upon-Tyne</entry>
<entry>Tyne &amp; Wear</entry>
<entry>NE1 4PA</entry>
</Address>
<Telephone><entry>03000 616161</entry>
</Telephone>
<Email><entry>enquiries@cqc.org.uk</entry>
</Email>
<ProviderServiceDetails><entry>Mon-Fri 8.30am-5.30pm</entry>
</ProviderServiceDetails>
<category><entry>CARE HOMES FOR OLDER PEOPLE (RESIDENTIAL HOMES)</entry>
<entry>CARE HOMES WITH NURSING FOR OLDER PEOPLE (NURSING HOMES)</entry>
</category>
</SheffieldHYS>
