<SheffieldHYS id="19386">
<BaseURL><entry>http://www.sheffieldhelpyourself.org.uk/full_search_new.asp?group=19386</entry>
</BaseURL>
<HYSID><entry>19386</entry>
</HYSID>
<OrgName><entry>VEOLIA ENVIRONMENTAL SERVICES PLC</entry>
</OrgName>
<AltName><entry>ONYX (FORMER NAME)</entry>
</AltName>
<Desc><entry>Collects and disposes of all the household waste in the city.  Includes the blue bin for paper and card, the green bin for garden waste (at the moment being trialled to 45,000 properties in Sheffield).   A new recycling service for householders is being rolled out across the city from April 2010-Nov 2010.  Under the new scheme blue bins take glass bottles, jars, tins, can and plastic bottles.  A blue box is for paper and card.  Both are collected on the same day every 2 weeks.  Provides a special service to people who cannot get their wheelie bin or box to the kerbside eg to people who have disabilities including visual impairment.  Has 5 Household Waste Recycling Centres and Recycling Bring sites.  Offers green sacks for a garden waste collection service and a bulky items collection service (including fridges and freezers).  For more information telephone 0114 273 4567.  Provides information on waste reduction, re-use and recycling.  Free information on recycling in Sheffield and up-to-date information on individual recycling schemes are also available.  Offers assistance to all voluntary sector recycling projects.</entry>
</Desc>
<Website><entry>http://www.veolia.co.uk/sheffield</entry>
</Website>
<Pubs><entry>Recycling information literature</entry>
</Pubs>
<Address><entry>Please contact for details</entry>
</Address>
<ContactName><entry>Gavin Foulstone, Recycling Manager/Annabel Johnston, Recycling Officer</entry>
</ContactName>
<Telephone><entry>0114 228 3630</entry>
<entry>Telephone 1 Details:</entry>
<entry>and answerphone</entry>
</Telephone>
<Fax><entry>0114 228 3661</entry>
</Fax>
<Email><entry>gavin.foulstone@veolia.co.uk</entry>
</Email>
<ProviderServiceDetails><entry>Mon-Fri 9am-5pm (by appointment only)</entry>
</ProviderServiceDetails>
<category><entry>ENVIRONMENT AND CONSERVATION</entry>
</category>
</SheffieldHYS>
