<SheffieldHYS id="19878">
<BaseURL><entry>http://www.sheffieldhelpyourself.org.uk/full_search_new.asp?group=19878</entry>
</BaseURL>
<HYSID><entry>19878</entry>
</HYSID>
<OrgName><entry>SCHOOLS AND HOMES ENERGY EDUCATION PROJECT</entry>
</OrgName>
<AltName><entry>SOLAR-ACTIVE</entry>
</AltName>
<Desc><entry>A social enterprise, company and charity which combines education, invention and manufacture to facilitate individuals and organisations making informed decisions about energy use at home, school and work.  Established recovery-insulation.co.uk to manufacture an environmentally friendly thermal and acoustic insulation made form recycled cotton textile fibres.  Energy use empowerment involves promoting low or no cost energy alternatives for local people, businesses and schools in Sheffield.  In association with Recovery Insulations and AfCE (Agency for Community Empowerment) has formed a support team to offer assistance to Sheffield Community Assemblies to promote energy efficiency and renewable energy applications in their area.  Has pioneered an education method and renewable and energy efficiency resources (solar car/boat, lorry, mini water pump) to make learning and teaching enjoyable, raise attainment in science and technology.  Runs design and technology/science and environment day demonstrations and activities, continuing professional development, family workshops, school and community Solar Challenges, solar water heating courses, carbon footprint, energy efficiency surveys and action plans, and support for joining the Eco-Schools progamme.</entry>
</Desc>
<Website><entry>http://www.pluggingintothesun.org.uk</entry>
</Website>
<Pubs><entry>Periodic reports; Case studies; Solar Electricity Resources/Guidelines; Solar Water Heating</entry>
</Pubs>
<CharityNo><entry>1073347</entry>
</CharityNo>
<Address><entry>Unit 12</entry>
<entry>53 Mowbray Street</entry>
<entry>Sheffield</entry>
<entry>South Yorkshire</entry>
<entry>S3 8EN</entry>
</Address>
<DisabledAccess><entry>Wheelchair Accessible;</entry>
<entry>Wheelchair Accessible with Assistance;</entry>
<entry>Wheelchair Accessible Toilet;</entry>
</DisabledAccess>
<ContactName><entry>David Garlovsky, Project Manager</entry>
</ContactName>
<Telephone><entry>0114 249 9459</entry>
</Telephone>
<Fax><entry>0114 249 9459</entry>
<entry>Minicom:</entry>
<entry>0114 249 9459</entry>
<entry>Mobile:</entry>
<entry>07968 844891</entry>
</Fax>
<Email><entry>enquiries@pluggingintothesun.org.uk</entry>
<entry>david@pluggingintothesun.org.uk</entry>
</Email>
<ProviderServiceDetails><entry>Mon-Fri 9am-4.30pm</entry>
</ProviderServiceDetails>
<category><entry>ENVIRONMENT AND CONSERVATION</entry>
</category>
</SheffieldHYS>
