<SheffieldHYS id="19911">
<BaseURL><entry>http://www.sheffieldhelpyourself.org.uk/full_search_new.asp?group=19911</entry>
</BaseURL>
<HYSID><entry>19911</entry>
</HYSID>
<OrgName><entry>SHARING CARING PROJECT</entry>
</OrgName>
<Desc><entry>The project supports family carers of adults with learning disabilities in Sheffield.  Supports families in their caring role and aims to enable them and the person they care for to have a good life and plan for the future with confidence.  Aims to remove barriers, inequalities and isolation that family carers often face.  

Offers: information, signposting, emotional support, newsletters, carer advocacy, support groups, individual support to help families get the help they may need now and in the future, support planning with families regarding their individual budgets and self-directed support, person-centred planning.  The project is part of Sheffield Mencap, which is a registered charity.</entry>
</Desc>
<Website><entry>http://www.sheffieldmencap.org.uk</entry>
</Website>
<Langs><entry>Punjabi, Urdu</entry>
</Langs>
<Pubs><entry>Newsletter</entry>
</Pubs>
<CharityNo><entry>1056155</entry>
</CharityNo>
<Address><entry>c/o Sheffield Mencap</entry>
<entry>Norfolk Lodge</entry>
<entry>Park Grange Road</entry>
<entry>Sheffield</entry>
<entry>South Yorkshire</entry>
<entry>S2 3QF</entry>
</Address>
<DisabledAccess><entry>Wheelchair Accessible;</entry>
<entry>Wheelchair Accessible Toilet;</entry>
</DisabledAccess>
<ContactName><entry>Dalia Magrill, SCP Co-ordinator</entry>
</ContactName>
<Telephone><entry>0114 275 8879</entry>
</Telephone>
<Fax><entry>0114 273 1227</entry>
</Fax>
<Email><entry>scpoffice@sharingcaring.org.uk</entry>
</Email>
<ProviderServiceDetails><entry>Mon-Fri 9am-4.30pm; for meeting venues and times, please contact for details</entry>
</ProviderServiceDetails>
<Provision><ProvisionPlace><entry>Please contact for details</entry>
</ProvisionPlace>
<ProvisionDaysAndTimes><entry>3rd Mon in the month (West group), 3rd Tues in the month (North group), alternate Weds (Pakistani women's carers group), 2nd we in the month (Wednesday lunch club), last Thurs in the month (South east group), 2nd Fri in the month (Central "Toastie" group).  Please contact the project if you wish to access a group or need help with tansport, the service has ring round lists and contacts eveyone before each group to confirm dates and times.</entry>
</ProvisionDaysAndTimes>
</Provision>
<category><entry>CARERS ORGANISATIONS</entry>
<entry>DIRECT PAYMENT SUPPORT</entry>
</category>
</SheffieldHYS>
