<SheffieldHYS id="22380">
<BaseURL><entry>http://www.sheffieldhelpyourself.org.uk/full_search_new.asp?group=22380</entry>
</BaseURL>
<HYSID><entry>22380</entry>
</HYSID>
<OrgName><entry>CLAYTON, RON</entry>
</OrgName>
<Desc><entry>Ron Clayton's subjects are: Sheffield Castle, The Inside Story; Up Loxley Bottoms; In Search of Robin Hood; Body Snatching in Sheffield; Garrison Town (the Military in Sheffield); A Fishmongers Lad (Growing Up in Hillsborough, Wadsley and Crookes 1952-1970); Lost Heritage (Historic Buildings in Sheffield Which Have Been Lost Since 1900); Gibbeted - The Story of Francis Fearn and Spence Broughton; Charlie Peace's Life, Loves and Crimes; Tha'll Stand the Drop of York, Some Orrible Sheffield Murders and Crimes; Some Famous Sheffield Ghosts and Hauntings; Harvey Teasdale, a Famous Sheffield Barmpot; The Lost Streets and Street Names of Sheffield; Sheffield's Greatest Chief Constable; Sheffield's Oldest Public House? (a look at the many faces of the Old Queen's Head Pub, Pond Hill); Sheffield and Sheffield Local History Quizzes.  Looking at Sheffield from Old Maps and Prints; An Evening with Ron Clayton, professional Sheffielder, wit and ractoneur; The Bar Maid's Apron - A Nostalgic Look Back at Sheffield's Vanishing Pub Heritage; Some Famous and Not So Famous Books About Sheffield; Historical walks around Sheffield can be arranged, please contact for further details.</entry>
</Desc>
<Pubs><entry>Leaflet; Books: Then and Now, Sheffield S6 Vol. 1; Ron Clayton's Hillsborough Legends (with Mark Rodgers); The River Loxley from Convergence to Confluence</entry>
</Pubs>
<Address><entry>8 Bankfield Road</entry>
<entry>Sheffield</entry>
<entry>South Yorkshire</entry>
<entry>S6 4RD</entry>
</Address>
<Telephone><entry>0114 234 6669</entry>
<entry>Telephone 1 Details:</entry>
<entry>and answerphone</entry>
<entry>Mobile:</entry>
<entry>07593 783608</entry>
</Telephone>
<Email><entry>bigronclayton@hotmail.co.uk</entry>
</Email>
<category><entry>SPEAKERS FOR MEETINGS</entry>
</category>
</SheffieldHYS>
