<SheffieldHYS id="22759">
<BaseURL><entry>http://www.sheffieldhelpyourself.org.uk/full_search_new.asp?group=22759</entry>
</BaseURL>
<HYSID><entry>22759</entry>
</HYSID>
<OrgName><entry>NSPCC INDEPENDENT VISITING SCHEME</entry>
</OrgName>
<Desc><entry>Available to all children/young people aged between 9-18 years (aged 18-24 years if care leavers), who have been "looked after" by Sheffield City Council's Children and Young Peoples Service for 6 months or more, have little or no contact (including supervised contact) with their parents and who would like an independent visitor.  Independent visitors are volunteers from all walks of life, who are trained and supported by the NSPCC and who listen, befriend and offer emotional and personal support to a child/young person in care; take a child/young person out on activities and help them socialise; accompany a child/young person to meetings such as reviews and/or support a child/young person through this process; enable a child/young person to express their wishes and feelings and to allow their voice to be heard.  It is expected that the Independent Visitor will visit a child/young person at least fortnightly and that the relationship will last at least a year.  A national registered charity, the NSPCC will meet travelling expenses and costs.  Self or any referral.</entry>
</Desc>
<CharityNo><entry>216401</entry>
</CharityNo>
<Address><entry>NSPCC Sheffield Young People's Centre</entry>
<entry>35 George Street</entry>
<entry>Sheffield</entry>
<entry>South Yorkshire</entry>
<entry>S1 2PF</entry>
</Address>
<DisabledAccess><entry>Wheelchair Accessible;</entry>
<entry>Wheelchair Accessible Toilet;</entry>
<entry>Lift</entry>
</DisabledAccess>
<ContactName><entry>Trish Cousins, Children's Services Manager</entry>
</ContactName>
<Telephone><entry>0114 228 9200</entry>
<entry>Telephone 1 Details:</entry>
<entry>Switchboard</entry>
<entry>0114 228 9263</entry>
<entry>Telephone 2 Details:</entry>
<entry>Independent visiting, and answerphone</entry>
</Telephone>
<Fax><entry>0114 228 9229</entry>
</Fax>
<Email><entry>sheffield@nspcc.org.uk</entry>
<entry>jboyle@nspcc.org.uk</entry>
</Email>
<ProviderServiceDetails><entry>Mon, Tues, Thurs &amp; Fri 9am-5pm, Wed 9am-6pm</entry>
</ProviderServiceDetails>
<category><entry>CHILDREN AND YOUNG PEOPLE - WELFARE AND SOCIAL INCLUSION</entry>
</category>
</SheffieldHYS>
