<SheffieldHYS id="23571">
<BaseURL><entry>http://www.sheffieldhelpyourself.org.uk/full_search_new.asp?group=23571</entry>
</BaseURL>
<HYSID><entry>23571</entry>
</HYSID>
<OrgName><entry>RECYCLING BRING BANK SITE - POSTAL DISTRICT 9</entry>
</OrgName>
<Desc><entry>B&amp;Q, Greenland Road - paper, glass, textiles, plastics, steel cans, card, shoes.  Bon Vin Wines, 340 Brightside Lane - glass.  Carbrook Council Offices, car park - glass.  Carbrook Hall Public House, Attercliffe Common - glass.  Don Valley Stadium, Attercliffe Road - glass.   Greenland Drive, Darnall - glass, steel cans, aluminium cans.  Londis, 1 Jenkin Drive - textiles.  Meadowhall Shopping Centre, Management Suite 1, The Oasis - paper, glass, textiles, plastics, steel cans, aluminium cans, shoes.  Phillimore Primary School, Phillimore Road - paper.   Royal Mail Main Office, Brightside Lane - glass, plastics, steel cans, aluminium cans.    Sheffield City Council, Staniforth Road - paper, glass.  Sheffield Ice, Attercliffe Road - glass.  South Yorkshire Housing, Basford Close - glass, steel cans, aluminium cans.  The Green Social Club, Senior Road - glass, shoes.  The Park, end of Greenland Close - glass, steel cans, aluminium cans.  Tinsley Green Community Centre, Norborough Road - glass, plastics, steel cans, aluminium cans.  Tinsley Junior School, Bawtry Road - paper.  Uttley Drive, Darnall - glass, steel cans, aluminium cans.</entry>
</Desc>
<Website><entry>http://www.veoliaenvironmentalservices.co.uk/sheffield</entry>
</Website>
<Address><entry>Veolia Environmental Services PLC</entry>
<entry>Lumley Street Service Centre</entry>
<entry>Lumley Street</entry>
<entry>Sheffield</entry>
<entry>South Yorkshire</entry>
<entry>S4 7ZJ</entry>
</Address>
<DisabledAccess><entry>Wheelchair Accessible;</entry>
<entry>Wheelchair Accessible Toilet;</entry>
</DisabledAccess>
<Telephone><entry>0114 273 4567</entry>
<entry>Telephone 1 Details:</entry>
<entry>Main Switchboard</entry>
<entry>0114 228 3630</entry>
<entry>Telephone 2 Details:</entry>
<entry>Office</entry>
</Telephone>
<category><entry>RECYCLING FACILITIES</entry>
</category>
</SheffieldHYS>
