<SheffieldHYS id="24178">
<BaseURL><entry>http://www.sheffieldhelpyourself.org.uk/full_search_new.asp?group=24178</entry>
</BaseURL>
<HYSID><entry>24178</entry>
</HYSID>
<OrgName><entry>SHEFFIELD CENTRE FOR INDEPENDENT LIVING DISABILTY INFORMATION SERVICE</entry>
</OrgName>
<AltName><entry>PACESETTERS INFORMATION SERVICE</entry>
</AltName>
<Desc><entry>Provides free, confidential information to disabled people, their families and friends, their personal assistants and carers and any other organisation or individual in Sheffield who needs information about disability related issues. Our information service is provided by staff and volunteers who have direct experience of disability themselves and understand the barriers that disabled people can face in accessing information. We aim to provide the information you require ourselves or, if we cannot do so, we will signpost you to an organisation that can. Free factsheets on a range of disability topics are available on our website.  Information is available in a range of formats to suit your requirements on request. Sheffield CIL Disability Information service is a member of DIAL UK  a national organisation with a network of approximately 120 Local Disability and Advice Line Services (DIALs) run by and for disabled people.  We are working towards the DIAL UK Quality Mark.</entry>
</Desc>
<Website><entry>http://www.sheffieldcil.org.uk</entry>
</Website>
<Langs><entry>By arrangement</entry>
</Langs>
<CharityNo><entry>1112712</entry>
</CharityNo>
<Address><entry>C/o Sheffield Centre for Independent Living (SCIL)</entry>
<entry>The Circle</entry>
<entry>33 Rockingham Lane</entry>
<entry>Sheffield</entry>
<entry>South Yorkshire</entry>
<entry>S1 4FW</entry>
</Address>
<ContactName><entry>Val Bowen</entry>
</ContactName>
<Telephone><entry>0114 253 6745</entry>
<entry>Telephone 1 Details:</entry>
<entry>Mon-Wed 10am-3pm</entry>
</Telephone>
<Email><entry>info@inclusivesheffield.org.uk</entry>
</Email>
<ProviderServiceDetails><entry>Mon-Wed 10am-3pm</entry>
</ProviderServiceDetails>
<category><entry>DISABLED PEOPLE - GENERAL SUPPORT</entry>
</category>
</SheffieldHYS>
