<SheffieldHYS id="24377">
<BaseURL><entry>http://www.sheffieldhelpyourself.org.uk/full_search_new.asp?group=24377</entry>
</BaseURL>
<HYSID><entry>24377</entry>
</HYSID>
<OrgName><entry>MULTIFAITH CHAPEL AND LIBRARY - BURNGREAVE ASHRAM</entry>
</OrgName>
<AltName><entry>BURNGREAVE INTERFAITH LIBRARY AND CHAPEL (FORMER NAME)</entry>
</AltName>
<Desc><entry>Available for reference and borrowing of books and printed matter for people of all faiths.  Holds lunchtime interfaith seminars.  Also meditation, prayer, discussion, reading and reflection, private study, research, interfaith events available to individuals and groups.  Project run by Ashram Community Trust (see separate entry).  Study of scriptural texts of all major faiths, textual reasoning, community (scriptural reflection, Saturday Forum on secular topics, visiting speakers and groups, pilgrimages retreats, interfaith tree planting, growing and environmental work in partnership with Sheffield City Council's Forestry Team, associated activities with Sheffield Interfaith, Sheffield Faith Forum and Islamic Society of Britain.  Works in partnership with Faith in action, Community Development Foundation Uk and the Department for Communities and Local Government.  Burngreave Ashram is a registered charity.</entry>
</Desc>
<Langs><entry>Arabic, Bengali, Farsi, Hindi, Panjabi, Sinhala</entry>
</Langs>
<Pubs><entry>Seminar papers, Interfaith Liturgies, Praying with Jesus (2010)</entry>
</Pubs>
<CharityNo><entry>1099164</entry>
</CharityNo>
<Address><entry>Burngreave Ashram</entry>
<entry>84-86 Spital Hill</entry>
<entry>Sheffield</entry>
<entry>South Yorkshire</entry>
<entry>S4 7LG</entry>
</Address>
<ContactName><entry>Nirmal Fernando/Ange</entry>
</ContactName>
<Telephone><entry>0114 270 0972</entry>
<entry>0208 961 5867</entry>
<entry>Mobile:</entry>
<entry>07932 017929</entry>
</Telephone>
<Email><entry>curlsu@hotmail.com</entry>
</Email>
<ProviderServiceDetails><entry>Mon-Fri 11.30am-5pm (opeing times), regular events held at other times, please contact for details</entry>
</ProviderServiceDetails>
<category><entry>RELIGIONS AND PHILOSOPHIES</entry>
</category>
</SheffieldHYS>
