<SheffieldHYS id="24502">
<BaseURL><entry>http://www.sheffieldhelpyourself.org.uk/full_search_new.asp?group=24502</entry>
</BaseURL>
<HYSID><entry>24502</entry>
</HYSID>
<OrgName><entry>YORKSHIRE AND HUMBER EMPLOYMENT AND LEARNING SKILLS SERVICE USER/CARER REFERENCE GROUP</entry>
</OrgName>
<AltName><entry>ELS REFERENCE GROUP</entry>
</AltName>
<Desc><entry>Regional mental health service user/carer group focusing on employment and learning skills, promoting consistency of approach re permitted earnings, addressing issues relating to employers, rural issues, young people in education, communication to reach service users who are not part of the group, contacting hard to reach groups including BME communities and developing regional service user involvement.  Seeks to make a meaningful contribution to developing national strategy and local delivery.  Aims to respond to the government agenda around delegating decision-making to the regions, feeds into regional policy delivery, contributes to regional strategy development, ensures that the service user's voice is heard, feeds into the national strategy on mental health and employment and comment on relevant parts of the new Department of Health and mental health strategy (New Horizons).  Comments on leaflets and other information produced by key agencies, ensuring that the group has a seat on other agencies' decision-making bodies and builds capacity in organisations around responding to people with mental health needs.  Membership of the group is dependent on submitting a successful application.  Members are paid for their attendance at meetings.</entry>
</Desc>
<Website><entry>http://www.yhip.org.uk/expertsbyexperience</entry>
</Website>
<Address><entry>The Circle</entry>
<entry>33 Rockingham Lane</entry>
<entry>Sheffield</entry>
<entry>South Yorkshire</entry>
<entry>S1 4FW</entry>
</Address>
<DisabledAccess><entry>Wheelchair Accessible;</entry>
<entry>Wheelchair Accessible Toilet;</entry>
</DisabledAccess>
<ContactName><entry>Patrick Wood</entry>
</ContactName>
<Telephone><entry>0114 253 6626</entry>
</Telephone>
<Email><entry>p.wood@vas.org.uk</entry>
</Email>
<Provision><ProvisionPlace><entry>Please contact for details</entry>
</ProvisionPlace>
<ProvisionDaysAndTimes><entry>Quarterly meetings</entry>
</ProvisionDaysAndTimes>
</Provision>
<category><entry>MENTAL HEALTH</entry>
</category>
</SheffieldHYS>
