<SheffieldHYS id="24810">
<BaseURL><entry>http://www.sheffieldhelpyourself.org.uk/full_search_new.asp?group=24810</entry>
</BaseURL>
<HYSID><entry>24810</entry>
</HYSID>
<OrgName><entry>CONFUCIUS INSTITUTE AT THE UNIVERSITY OF SHEFFIELD (SCI)</entry>
</OrgName>
<Desc><entry>The Confucius Institute is an international collaboration between the University of Sheffield, the Office of Chinese Language Council International (OCLCI, commonly known as Hanban), Beijing Language and Culture University and Nanjing University, which focuses on China-related activities, fostering the provision of innovative and flexible non-degree Chinese language and cultural learning courses for the wider community.  Offers Mandarin language courses including one-to-one tuition, taster sessions, professional/business Chinese, evening classes, and short course intensives.  Cultural courses include calligraphy, Taiji (Tai Chi - see separate entry) and Guzheng (chinese zither).</entry>
</Desc>
<Website><entry>http://www.shef.ac.uk/confucius</entry>
</Website>
<Langs><entry>Mandarin</entry>
</Langs>
<Pubs><entry>Confucius Institute Newsletter (in English); Confucius Institute News Briefing (in Chinese)</entry>
</Pubs>
<CharityNo><entry>X 1089</entry>
</CharityNo>
<Address><entry>5 Shearwood Road</entry>
<entry>Sheffield</entry>
<entry>South Yorkshire</entry>
<entry>S10 2TD</entry>
</Address>
<ContactName><entry>Miss Caterina Webber</entry>
</ContactName>
<Telephone><entry>0114 222 8332</entry>
</Telephone>
<Fax><entry>0114 222 8334</entry>
</Fax>
<Email><entry>confucius@sheffield.ac.uk</entry>
</Email>
<ProviderServiceDetails><entry>Weekday evenings 5-6pm or 6-7pm (Chinese zither classes), university semester times only, please contact for details</entry>
</ProviderServiceDetails>
<Provision><ProvisionPlace><entry>Hicks Building</entry>
<entry>Hounsfield Road</entry>
<entry>Sheffield</entry>
<entry>South Yorkshire</entry>
<entry>S3 7RH</entry>
</ProvisionPlace>
<ProvisionDaysAndTimes><entry>Weekday evenings 7-9pm (Language courses and calligraphy course), university semester times only, please contact for details</entry>
</ProvisionDaysAndTimes>
</Provision>
<category><entry>BLACK AND MINORITY ETHNIC PEOPLE - COMMUNITY ORGANISATIONS</entry>
</category>
</SheffieldHYS>
