<SheffieldHYS id="24975">
<BaseURL><entry>http://www.sheffieldhelpyourself.org.uk/full_search_new.asp?group=24975</entry>
</BaseURL>
<HYSID><entry>24975</entry>
</HYSID>
<OrgName><entry>CARERS EMERGENCY SUPPORT TEAM</entry>
</OrgName>
<Desc><entry>A new social work team based at the Sheffield Carers Centre which supports carers of older people and those they care for to develop emergency care plans which can be put in place at any time at which care has to stop, for any reason. If plans like this are made in advance then families are not left to rely on standard services being found at the last minute by their social workers but would know that if need be, their own personal plans are there to be put in place. The team recognises that carers are experts in the care they provide and should therefore be central to care planning, both for the long term and for emergencies.  In the long term the team will be able to work with any carers who care for someone over the age of sixty five who is eligible for support from social services, even if they have chosen not to accept this.  A social care assessment must however have taken place. If you would like to access this service but have had no prior contact with social services, this can be made by speaking to the access team for older peoples services on 0114 2734908.</entry>
</Desc>
<Address><entry>Sheffield Carers Centre</entry>
<entry>7 Bells Court</entry>
<entry>Bells Square</entry>
<entry>Sheffield</entry>
<entry>South Yorkshire</entry>
<entry>S1 2FY</entry>
</Address>
<DisabledAccess><entry>Wheelchair Accessible;</entry>
<entry>Wheelchair Accessible Toilet;</entry>
</DisabledAccess>
<ContactName><entry>Anna Robottom/Deborah Senior</entry>
</ContactName>
<Telephone><entry>0114 252 1912</entry>
<entry>Telephone 1 Details:</entry>
<entry>and anwerphone</entry>
</Telephone>
<Email><entry>opcest@sheffield.gov.uk</entry>
</Email>
<ProviderServiceDetails><entry>Mon-Thurs 8.45am-5.15pm, Fri 8.45am-4.45pm</entry>
</ProviderServiceDetails>
<category><entry>CARERS ORGANISATIONS</entry>
</category>
</SheffieldHYS>
