<SheffieldHYS id="25024">
<BaseURL><entry>http://www.sheffieldhelpyourself.org.uk/full_search_new.asp?group=25024</entry>
</BaseURL>
<HYSID><entry>25024</entry>
</HYSID>
<OrgName><entry>MANOR OAKS FARM - GREEN ESTATE</entry>
</OrgName>
<Desc><entry>The Manor Oaks Farm is a new social enterprise project run in partnership with the Burton Street Project (see separate entry) and supported by the Big Lottery/Local Food.  The aim of the project is to develop an environmentally friendly and sustainable farming enterprise, working closely with people who have learning disabilities and mental health problems, helping them to get involved with the farms operation and the local community.  Green Estate is in the process of turning 4 acres of land on the Manor Lodge estate into a collection of orchards, vegetable patches and grazing areas.  Producing fruit and vegetables etc. to sell in the on-site farm shop and community resource café.  The project also aims to invite the local community and school children to visit the farm, offering them the opportunity to learn about sustainable farming practices, seeking to reconnect people with their rural roots and the heritage of the area.  By demonstrating the skills required to work the farm land and grow produce for sale the scheme hopes to increase visitors awarness of nature and the origin of their food.  A registered charity</entry>
</Desc>
<Website><entry>http://www.greenestate.org.uk</entry>
</Website>
<Langs><entry>Portugese, Spanish</entry>
</Langs>
<Pubs><entry>Leaflets</entry>
</Pubs>
<CharityNo><entry>1099954</entry>
</CharityNo>
<Address><entry>Green Estate</entry>
<entry>389 Manor Lane</entry>
<entry>Sheffield</entry>
<entry>South Yorkshire</entry>
<entry>S2 1UL</entry>
</Address>
<ContactName><entry>Milena Harbach, Farm Enterprise Manager/Mike Evans</entry>
</ContactName>
<Telephone><entry>0114 276 2828</entry>
<entry>0114 267 7627</entry>
<entry>Mobile:</entry>
<entry>07789 692204</entry>
</Telephone>
<Email><entry>m.harbach@greenestate.org</entry>
<entry>m.evans@greenestate.org</entry>
</Email>
<ProviderServiceDetails><entry>Mon-Fri 8am-5pm</entry>
</ProviderServiceDetails>
<category><entry>CITY FARMS</entry>
<entry>LEARNING DISABILITIES - ORGANISATIONS FOR PEOPLE WITH</entry>
<entry>MENTAL HEALTH</entry>
</category>
</SheffieldHYS>
