<SheffieldHYS id="16443">
<BaseURL><entry>http://www.sheffieldhelpyourself.org.uk/full_search_new.asp?group=16443</entry>
</BaseURL>
<HYSID><entry>16443</entry>
</HYSID>
<OrgName><entry>ACTION SPACE MOBILE</entry>
</OrgName>
<Desc><entry>A registered charity and community arts organisation working locally, nationally and internationally to create opportunities for individuals and communities to participate in the arts, based on the belief that arts activity can change lives.  Activities and events can be devised and delivered with the participants needs in mind using the skills of an artistic team whose talents span visual arts, craft, movement, dance, music (instrumental, vocal and compositional), storytelling, puppetry, film and digital projections.  The core work of the organisation is creative work with adults and children with learning disabilities.  This is exemplified in three long standing and ongoing projects: In the Boat Theatre Company based in Sheffield, Cross the Sky Theatre Company (see separate entry) based in Barnsley, and a Visibility school holiday arts programme for children run in Sheffield, Barnsley and Wakefield.</entry>
</Desc>
<Website><entry>http://www.actionspacemobile.org/</entry>
</Website>
<Langs><entry>French, German, Romanian</entry>
</Langs>
<Pubs><entry>Waterworks, booklet and video for schools, Key Stage 1 and 2; This Is How We Do It, art work for adults with special needs</entry>
</Pubs>
<CharityNo><entry>289609</entry>
</CharityNo>
<Address><entry>Mapplewell and Staincross Village Hall</entry>
<entry>Darton Lane</entry>
<entry>Barnsley</entry>
<entry>South Yorkshire</entry>
<entry>S75 6AL</entry>
</Address>
<ContactName><entry>Ruth Jones, Company Manager and Richard Rawson, Administrator</entry>
</ContactName>
<Telephone><entry>01226 391112</entry>
</Telephone>
<Email><entry>contact@actionspacemobile.org</entry>
</Email>
<ProviderServiceDetails><entry>Mon-Fri 9am-5pm (office times)</entry>
</ProviderServiceDetails>
<Provision><ProvisionPlace><entry>The Institute</entry>
<entry>Heeley Development Trust</entry>
<entry>147 Gleadless Road</entry>
<entry>Sheffield</entry>
<entry>South Yorkshire</entry>
<entry>S2 3AF</entry>
</ProvisionPlace>
<ProvisionPlaceDisabledAccess><entry>Wheelchair Accessible;</entry>
<entry>Wheelchair Accessible Toilet;</entry>
<entry>Further Access Details:</entry>
<entry>Large car park</entry>
</ProvisionPlaceDisabledAccess>
<ProvisionDaysAndTimes><entry>Fri 9.30am-3.30pm (In the Boat Theatre Company)</entry>
</ProvisionDaysAndTimes>
</Provision>
<category><entry>DISABLED PEOPLE - GENERAL SUPPORT</entry>
</category>
</SheffieldHYS>
