<SheffieldHYS id="16442">
<BaseURL><entry>http://www.sheffieldhelpyourself.org.uk/full_search_new.asp?group=16442</entry>
</BaseURL>
<HYSID><entry>16442</entry>
</HYSID>
<OrgName><entry>ACTION HOUSING AND SUPPORT</entry>
</OrgName>
<Desc><entry>A registered charity and voluntary organisation which provides supported accommodation to vulnerable and marginalised people who may be offenders, ex-offenders, those likely to offend, have support needs with substance misuse, mental health, domestic violence or other issues requiring support.  Supported accommodation is suitable for single people 18 years and over initially shared accommodation will be allocated if the client is suitable for this project.  The accommodation is dispersed in the Sheffield area.  Support is available for up to 2 years.  Aims to move clients into self-contained accommodation where appropriate once clients are living more independently.  An agreed support plan will be agreed by the client and their key worker so that the client can work towards their goals to enable them to live more independently in the future.  Referrals are welcomed by the Probation Service, social workers, substance misuse agencies, health professionals, GPs as well as other agencies.  People can also self-refer, assistance with this can be offered.  Sheffield also have an Outreach Project offering short term support up to 3 months to assist with housing related issues.  Support referrals are accepted via the Probation service.</entry>
</Desc>
<Website><entry>http://www.actionhousinguk.org</entry>
</Website>
<Langs><entry>By arrangement</entry>
</Langs>
<Pubs><entry>Leaflet</entry>
</Pubs>
<CharityNo><entry>511265</entry>
</CharityNo>
<Address><entry>Blenheim House</entry>
<entry>22 Wilkinson Street</entry>
<entry>Sheffield</entry>
<entry>South Yorkshire</entry>
<entry>S10 2GB</entry>
</Address>
<DisabledAccess><entry>Wheelchair Accessible with Assistance;</entry>
<entry>Wheelchair Accessible Toilet;</entry>
</DisabledAccess>
<ContactName><entry>Ken Howlett/Helen Caulfield-Browne/Mark Gillen</entry>
</ContactName>
<Telephone><entry>0114 249 6575</entry>
</Telephone>
<Fax><entry>0114 249 6579</entry>
</Fax>
<Email><entry>mark.gillen@actionhousinguk.org</entry>
<entry>helen.caulfield-browne@actionhousinguk.org</entry>
</Email>
<ProviderServiceDetails><entry>Mon-Fri 9am-5pm</entry>
</ProviderServiceDetails>
<category><entry>HOUSING, ADVICE AND SUPPORT FOR HOMELESS OR VULNERABLE PEOPLE</entry>
</category>
</SheffieldHYS>
