<SheffieldHYS id="16476">
<BaseURL><entry>http://www.sheffieldhelpyourself.org.uk/full_search_new.asp?group=16476</entry>
</BaseURL>
<HYSID><entry>16476</entry>
</HYSID>
<OrgName><entry>AGEWELL AND LUNCH CLUBS IN SHEFFIELD (ALIS)</entry>
</OrgName>
<Desc><entry>A registered charity which works on community development and health with people aged 50 years and over who are resident in the Sheffield district.  Supports and develops Agewell groups that meet on a weekly basis to provide a 12 weekly cycle of health related activities for older people.  Activities include gentle exercise, games, quizzes, reminiscence talks and presentations on a wide range of subjects.  Runs a volunteer based project  where volunteers will cut overgrown hedges, lawns, fit security chains etc (see separate entry).  Also supports and develops lunch clubs in all areas of the city that provide a hot meal for anyone who needs social interaction.  Provides a referral scheme whereby GPs, community health staff, social workers, family and friends can refer older isolated people to the charity.  People can also refer themselves.  Clients are then visited and supported to enable them to join their nearest Agewell group or lunch club.  Company limited by guarantee no 03374012.</entry>
</Desc>
<Website><entry>http://www.agewell.co.uk</entry>
</Website>
<CharityNo><entry>1064527</entry>
</CharityNo>
<Address><entry>135 Upperthorpe Road</entry>
<entry>Sheffield</entry>
<entry>South Yorkshire</entry>
<entry>S6 3EB</entry>
</Address>
<DisabledAccess><entry>Wheelchair Accessible Toilet;</entry>
<entry>Chairlift to first floor.  Wheelchair and disabled toilet on ground floor.</entry>
</DisabledAccess>
<ContactName><entry>Lisa Sollitt-Pass, Senior Development Officer/Rod McNamara, Chief Executive Officer/Julie White, Admin &amp; Support Officer</entry>
</ContactName>
<Telephone><entry>0114 275 1212</entry>
<entry>Telephone 1 Details:</entry>
<entry>and answerphone</entry>
<entry>0114 275 8007</entry>
<entry>Telephone 2 Details:</entry>
<entry>New Referrals</entry>
</Telephone>
<Fax><entry>0114 278 4887</entry>
</Fax>
<Email><entry>julie.agewell@googlemail.com</entry>
<entry>lisa.sollitpass@googlemail.com</entry>
</Email>
<ProviderServiceDetails><entry>Mon-Fri 10am-4pm</entry>
</ProviderServiceDetails>
<Provision><ProvisionPlace><entry>Please contact for details</entry>
</ProvisionPlace>
<ProvisionDaysAndTimes><entry>Monthly (support meeting for volunteers), monthly (Committee Meeting), quarterly (forum for group leaders)</entry>
</ProvisionDaysAndTimes>
</Provision>
<category><entry>OLDER PEOPLE - ORGANISATIONS FOR</entry>
</category>
</SheffieldHYS>
