<SheffieldHYS id="17072">
<BaseURL><entry>http://www.sheffieldhelpyourself.org.uk/full_search_new.asp?group=17072</entry>
</BaseURL>
<HYSID><entry>17072</entry>
</HYSID>
<OrgName><entry>CENTRAL CHILDRENS AND YOUNG PEOPLES LIBRARY</entry>
</OrgName>
<Desc><entry>Part of Sheffield Libraries, Archives and Information.  Provides a comprehensive library service to children, young people and families in a welcoming environment.  Offers lending facilities for books, talking books on tape and CD, DVDs, dual language material and limited special needs material.  There is a small reference collection, a public access catalogue and three People's Network computers for children's use.  Comfortable area for toddlers reading and play.  Regular activities include pre-school Story Time session, with related activities, baby and toddler sessions, Chatterbooks reading group for 8-12 year olds and Books Aloud reading group for young adults.  Also holiday activities and a programme of promotional reading events for children and families.  There is also a homework zone where staff are on hand to suggest relevant books or websites.  Groups and class visits by arrangement.  Toilet and baby changing facilities available.</entry>
</Desc>
<Website><entry>http://www.sheffield.gov.uk/libraries</entry>
</Website>
<Address><entry>Central Library</entry>
<entry>Surrey Street</entry>
<entry>Sheffield</entry>
<entry>South Yorkshire</entry>
<entry>S1 1XZ</entry>
</Address>
<DisabledAccess><entry>Wheelchair Accessible with Assistance;</entry>
<entry>Wheelchair Accessible Toilet;</entry>
<entry>Baby change facilities available</entry>
</DisabledAccess>
<Telephone><entry>0114 273 4734</entry>
</Telephone>
<Fax><entry>0114 273 5009</entry>
</Fax>
<Email><entry>kidsandteens.library@sheffield.gov.uk</entry>
</Email>
<ProviderServiceDetails><entry>Mon-Fri 10.30am-5.30pm, Sat 9.30am-5.30pm; Mon 10.45am-12noon (pre-school Story Time session, term-time only), Fri 10.30-12noon (baby and toddler session, term-time only)</entry>
</ProviderServiceDetails>
<category><entry>LIBRARIES, ARCHIVES AND INFORMATION SERVICES</entry>
</category>
</SheffieldHYS>
