<SheffieldHYS id="17257">
<BaseURL><entry>http://www.sheffieldhelpyourself.org.uk/full_search_new.asp?group=17257</entry>
</BaseURL>
<HYSID><entry>17257</entry>
</HYSID>
<OrgName><entry>CITY WIDE CARE ALARMS SERVICE</entry>
</OrgName>
<AltName><entry>CARE4YOU - CITY WIDE CARE ALARMS</entry>
</AltName>
<Desc><entry>A care alarm service which allows people to get help when they are in difficulty.  A portable alarm button and a unit with a powerful speaker and microphone are installed, which works via the telephone line.  When the alarm button is pressed, a call is put through to a control centre, which is staffed 24 hours a day, 7 days a week and appropriate help is organised.  The service provides mobile wardens who are all professionally trained and well equipped.  They can provide emergency personal care support and help lift people who may have fallen.  The service is available to anyone over 18 living in Sheffield who feels they could benefit from the security it provides.  This can include older people, people who have recently left hospital, people with disabilities, are living alone or are subject to harassment.  There is a weekly charge and payment can be arranged monthly or quarterly.  Additional alarms can also be added which automatically monitor situations, such as escaping smoke, gas or carbon monoxide, overflowing baths or sinks, whether someone has fallen, not returned to bed within a set time or has wandered out of their property at an inappropriate time.  In the future it is hoped that City Wide Care Alarms will begin supplying alarms which will solely alert someone in the property or a near by carer and not be connected to the call monitoring centre.  This is to provide extra support to help people live safely and independently in their own home and to provide extra support for people acting as a carer.</entry>
</Desc>
<Website><entry>http://www.sheffield.gov.uk/carealarms</entry>
</Website>
<Pubs><entry>Leaflet</entry>
</Pubs>
<Address><entry>Neighbourhoods and Community Care Directorate</entry>
<entry>Floor 1</entry>
<entry>Priory Office</entry>
<entry>Station Road</entry>
<entry>Sheffield</entry>
<entry>South Yorkshire</entry>
<entry>S9 4JT</entry>
</Address>
<DisabledAccess><entry>Wheelchair Accessible;</entry>
<entry>Wheelchair Accessible Toilet;</entry>
</DisabledAccess>
<ContactName><entry>Jackie Young, Registered Manager/Kath Cotton, Deputy Manager/Vicky Green, Business Support Team Leader</entry>
</ContactName>
<Telephone><entry>0800 013 0980</entry>
<entry>Telephone 1 Details:</entry>
<entry>Freephone</entry>
<entry>0114 242 0351</entry>
<entry>Telephone 3:</entry>
<entry>0114 273 4843</entry>
<entry>Telephone 3 Details:</entry>
<entry>Out of hours</entry>
</Telephone>
<Fax><entry>0114 203 7541</entry>
</Fax>
<Email><entry>citywidecarealarms@sheffield.gov.uk</entry>
</Email>
<ProviderServiceDetails><entry>Mon-Thurs 9am-5pm, Fri 9am-4.45pm (office), Mon-Sun 24h (Alarm service)</entry>
</ProviderServiceDetails>
<category><entry>COMMUNITY SAFETY</entry>
</category>
</SheffieldHYS>
