<SheffieldHYS id="17868">
<BaseURL><entry>http://www.sheffieldhelpyourself.org.uk/full_search_new.asp?group=17868</entry>
</BaseURL>
<HYSID><entry>17868</entry>
</HYSID>
<OrgName><entry>LIFELONG LEARNING AND SKILLS SERVICE - FAMILY LEARNING</entry>
</OrgName>
<Desc><entry>Part of Sheffield City Council.  Aims to encourage parental involvement in schools and voluntary and community settings, particularly in areas of social and educational disadvantage.  Offers free learning programmes for families (both adult and children) that aim to promote a lifelong love of learning together as a family, helps both adults and children to improve their skills particularly in the areas of literacy and numeracy and helps adults to better support their children's learning.  Programmes are delivered by specialist family learning staff in Children's Centres, Sure Start, schools, community and voluntary settings across the whole of the city.  Families that participate report an increase in their skills, an increase in their confidence around learning, improved relationships both with each other and with schools, Children's Centres etc and gains in qualifications that lead to further learning, volunteering or employment.</entry>
</Desc>
<Website><entry>http://www.sheffield.gov.uk/education/information-for-learners/familylearning</entry>
</Website>
<Pubs><entry>Leaflet, available in Arabic, Bangladeshi, Chinese, Somali, Urdu</entry>
</Pubs>
<Address><entry>145 Crookesmoor Road</entry>
<entry>Sheffield</entry>
<entry>South Yorkshire</entry>
<entry>S6 3FP</entry>
</Address>
<DisabledAccess><entry>Wheelchair Accessible;</entry>
<entry>Wheelchair Accessible Toilet;</entry>
<entry>Lift</entry>
</DisabledAccess>
<ContactName><entry>Karen Hanson/Sue Moore/Angela Staley/Carol Woodcock</entry>
</ContactName>
<Telephone><entry>0114 266 7503</entry>
</Telephone>
<Fax><entry>0114 266 7092</entry>
</Fax>
<Email><entry>karen.hanson@sheffield.gov.uk</entry>
</Email>
<ProviderServiceDetails><entry>Mon-Fri 9am-5pm</entry>
</ProviderServiceDetails>
<category><entry>CHILDHOOD EDUCATION</entry>
</category>
</SheffieldHYS>
