<SheffieldHYS id="18022">
<BaseURL><entry>http://www.sheffieldhelpyourself.org.uk/full_search_new.asp?group=18022</entry>
</BaseURL>
<HYSID><entry>18022</entry>
</HYSID>
<OrgName><entry>FRIENDS OF THE PORTER VALLEY</entry>
</OrgName>
<Desc><entry>A registered charity whose primary aim is the conservation of the Porter Valley area from Hunters Bar to Porter Clough.  Co-ordinates and obtains funding for major works such as repairing dams.  Collects information on the current and historical status of species diversity and man-made artefacts within the area.  Has published detailed reports which survey the ecology, butterflies, archaeology, geology, field systems and rivers (Porter and Maybrook) in the area.  Also has a published report on the mines and quarries at Ringinglow.  All reports are for sale.  Has an Oral History project, interviewing older residents to record valuable information about the area in past times.  This will be used in a published report on Agriculture and the Allotments.  Monitors planning applications and makes objections when necessary.  Works with Sheffield City Council Parks Department and Rangers.  Conducts other activities eg information weeks.  Actively fundraising for the restoration of Shepherd Wheel, Dam and workshops.</entry>
</Desc>
<Website><entry>http://www.sheffieldportervalley.org.uk</entry>
</Website>
<Pubs><entry>Porter Valley News</entry>
</Pubs>
<CharityNo><entry>1069865</entry>
</CharityNo>
<Address><entry>Please contact for details</entry>
</Address>
<ContactName><entry>Flora Owen, Secretary</entry>
</ContactName>
<Telephone><entry>0114 230 1345</entry>
<entry>Mobile:</entry>
<entry>07941 613939</entry>
</Telephone>
<Email><entry>floraowen55@hotmail.com</entry>
</Email>
<Provision><ProvisionPlace><entry>Various venues</entry>
<entry>please contact for details</entry>
</ProvisionPlace>
<ProvisionDaysAndTimes><entry>Monthly (outdoor events)</entry>
</ProvisionDaysAndTimes>
<ProvisionPlace><entry>Bents Green Methodist Church</entry>
<entry>Ringinglow Road</entry>
<entry>Sheffield</entry>
<entry>South Yorkshire</entry>
<entry>S11 7PU</entry>
</ProvisionPlace>
<ProvisionPlaceDisabledAccess><entry>Wheelchair Accessible;</entry>
<entry>Wheelchair Accessible Toilet;</entry>
</ProvisionPlaceDisabledAccess>
<ProvisionDaysAndTimes><entry>Usually 1st Wed in the month, quarterly at 7.30pm (Feb, May, Aug and Nov)</entry>
</ProvisionDaysAndTimes>
</Provision>
<category><entry>ENVIRONMENT AND CONSERVATION</entry>
</category>
</SheffieldHYS>
