<SheffieldHYS id="18791">
<BaseURL><entry>http://www.sheffieldhelpyourself.org.uk/full_search_new.asp?group=18791</entry>
</BaseURL>
<HYSID><entry>18791</entry>
</HYSID>
<OrgName><entry>SCHOOLS AND YOUNG PEOPLES LIBRARY SERVICE</entry>
</OrgName>
<Desc><entry>Part of Sheffield Libraries, Archives and Information.  An integrated children's and young people's service which is responsible for services to children through the public library and the Schools Library Service.  Oversees children's services activities and reading promotion projects in community libraries and the Central Children's Library.  Responsible for policies relating to children, stock purchase, summer reading challenge and other initiatives.  Provides Bookstart and Bookstart Plus for children aged under 5 years and Baby Time sessions in all libraries.  Runs the Sheffield Children's Book Awards annually.  Schools Library Service provides a subscription service to all Sheffield schools and educationalists.  This includes a showroom for selecting materials, a project loan service, van deliveries, and help and advice on the organisation and development of school libraries.</entry>
</Desc>
<Website><entry>http://www.sheffield.gov.uk/libraries</entry>
</Website>
<Address><entry>c/o Bannerdale Centre</entry>
<entry>125 Carter Knowle Road</entry>
<entry>Sheffield</entry>
<entry>South Yorkshire</entry>
<entry>S7 2EX</entry>
</Address>
<DisabledAccess><entry>Wheelchair Accessible with Assistance;</entry>
<entry>Wheelchair Accessible Toilet;</entry>
</DisabledAccess>
<ContactName><entry>Diane Kostka, Manager</entry>
</ContactName>
<Telephone><entry>0114 250 6840</entry>
<entry>Telephone 1 Details:</entry>
<entry>Schools Library Service Counter</entry>
<entry>0114 250 6844</entry>
<entry>Telephone 2 Details:</entry>
<entry>Young People's Team/Children's Book Awards</entry>
<entry>Telephone 3:</entry>
<entry>0114 250 6839</entry>
</Telephone>
<Fax><entry>0114 250 6841</entry>
</Fax>
<Email><entry>schoolslibraryservice@sheffield.gov.uk</entry>
</Email>
<ProviderServiceDetails><entry>Mon-Thurs 12noon-6pm (term-time), 1st Sat of each term 9am-12.30pm, Mon-Thurs 9am-5pm (school holidays), the service is closed for 2 weeks at the beginning of August, please check for details</entry>
</ProviderServiceDetails>
<category><entry>LIBRARIES, ARCHIVES AND INFORMATION SERVICES</entry>
</category>
</SheffieldHYS>
