<SheffieldHYS id="20362">
<BaseURL><entry>http://www.sheffieldhelpyourself.org.uk/full_search_new.asp?group=20362</entry>
</BaseURL>
<HYSID><entry>20362</entry>
</HYSID>
<OrgName><entry>SHEFFIELD MIND LTD</entry>
</OrgName>
<Desc><entry>A registered charity that provides information to people with mental health problems, their relatives, carers, the public and health professionals about services available.  Runs a counselling service offering one-to-one counselling and psychotherapy for up to a year.  Also offers a number of short and longer term therapeutic groups.  Hosts the Sheffield Mind and Body Project which runs a range of activities around the Firth Park and Manor &amp; Castle areas (workshops, groups and one to one mentoring, see separate entry) to help people improve their mental and physical wellbeing through physical activity and healthy eating.  Sheffield Mind produces the Sheffield Mental Health Guide - a booklet and web based resource for Sheffield.  All services are free and available to anyone aged 16 years and over living in Sheffield.  Free creche available.  Also provides services for individuals in receipt of a personal budget under Self Directed Support.  These include: Budget Management Service, holding your budget, paying invoices, providing regular statements and telephone support. Support Planning; helping you to plan your support using Sheffield Mind's broad knowledge of mental health and other services in the city.  Befriending; a befriender can provide support to undertake social activities such as going to the cinema, football etc, for up to 4 hours a week.  A Support Worker; providing support to help with most aspects of daily living for up to 8 hours a week.  For more information please visit www.sheffieldmentalhealth.org.uk/other-support/self-directed-support.  Resources include self-help leaflets and rooms for hire.  Company limited by guarantee no 1336352.  Self or any referral.</entry>
</Desc>
<Website><entry>http://www.sheffieldmind.co.uk</entry>
</Website>
<Pubs><entry>Annual Report; Sheffield Mental Health Guide</entry>
</Pubs>
<CharityNo><entry>276108</entry>
</CharityNo>
<Address><entry>57 Wostenholm Road</entry>
<entry>Sheffield</entry>
<entry>South Yorkshire</entry>
<entry>S7 1LE</entry>
</Address>
<Telephone><entry>0114 258 4489</entry>
<entry>Telephone 1 Details:</entry>
<entry>and answerphone</entry>
</Telephone>
<Fax><entry>0114 250 0729</entry>
</Fax>
<Email><entry>info@sheffieldmind.co.uk</entry>
</Email>
<ProviderServiceDetails><entry>Mon-Fri 9am-5m, counselling service by arrangement</entry>
</ProviderServiceDetails>
<category><entry>DIRECT PAYMENT SUPPORT</entry>
<entry>MENTAL HEALTH</entry>
</category>
</SheffieldHYS>
