<SheffieldHYS id="20652">
<BaseURL><entry>http://www.sheffieldhelpyourself.org.uk/full_search_new.asp?group=20652</entry>
</BaseURL>
<HYSID><entry>20652</entry>
</HYSID>
<OrgName><entry>SHEFFIELD CITY COUNCIL SMALL GRANTS FUND</entry>
</OrgName>
<AltName><entry>SHEFFIELD CITY COUNCIL GRANT AID (FORMER NAME)</entry>
</AltName>
<Desc><entry>A simple, fast track grant scheme for projects that want to make a difference in their local community.  Keen to fund small voluntary, community and self-help projects run by and for local people.  Prioritises activities that: promote community cohesion, reduce social exclusion and inequalities, promote community well-being and active citizenship.  Projects can apply for any amount up to £4,000 in a year and do not need to have a formal constitution or be a registered charity to apply but do need to have a bank account in the name of the group.  The fund does not give grants for food, costs for the benefit of individuals or groups with large unrestricted funds or a high annual income.  Also administers the Strengthening Communities Small Grants Fund which offers up to £3,000 for projects that encourage and develop dialogue between communities, promote cohesion and challenge extremism; the First Steps Fund for Older People which makes grants of up to £500 to new groups and existing groups undertaking new activities for older people; t and the Kids Can Do Fund for positive activities for 8-13 year olds (see separate entry).</entry>
</Desc>
<Website><entry>http://www.sheffield.gov.uk/smallgrants</entry>
</Website>
<Langs><entry>By arrangement</entry>
</Langs>
<Pubs><entry>Funding Forum/Funding News</entry>
</Pubs>
<Address><entry>Voluntary Sector Liaison Team</entry>
<entry>Sheffield City Council</entry>
<entry>Town Hall</entry>
<entry>Surrey Street</entry>
<entry>Sheffield</entry>
<entry>South Yorkshire</entry>
<entry>S1 2HH</entry>
</Address>
<DisabledAccess><entry>Wheelchair Accessible with Assistance;</entry>
<entry>Wheelchair Accessible Toilet;</entry>
</DisabledAccess>
<Telephone><entry>0114 273 4113</entry>
<entry>Telephone 1 Details:</entry>
<entry>Funding enquiries and answerphone</entry>
</Telephone>
<Fax><entry>0114 273 6878</entry>
</Fax>
<Email><entry>vslt@sheffield.gov.uk</entry>
</Email>
<ProviderServiceDetails><entry>Mon-Fri 9am-5pm, by appointment only</entry>
</ProviderServiceDetails>
<category><entry>FUNDING FOR GROUPS</entry>
</category>
</SheffieldHYS>
