<SheffieldHYS id="21347">
<BaseURL><entry>http://www.sheffieldhelpyourself.org.uk/full_search_new.asp?group=21347</entry>
</BaseURL>
<HYSID><entry>21347</entry>
</HYSID>
<OrgName><entry>ULLEY SAILING CLUB</entry>
</OrgName>
<Desc><entry>A small friendly sailing club located between Rotherham and Sheffield catering for both racing and casual sailing.  Families are especially welcome and the emphasis is on enjoyment and not just out and out racing.  Aims to promote the sport of sailing within the community and at an affordable price.  Has several RYA registered training instructors who  train both adults and younger members and can cover various aspects of dinghy sailing.  Saturdays are usually devoted to casual sailing.  For racers sailing takes place on Sundays and also on Wednesday evenings from Spring to Autumn.  The Enterprise, Laser, Splash and Streaker dinghy classes are well represented at the club and there are several club boats available for hire by club members.  The sailing calendar is vast and varied and normally includes social events.  Organises a sailing series known as The Frostbite each Sunday during November and December for the hardy.</entry>
</Desc>
<Website><entry>http://www.ulleysailingclub.org.uk</entry>
</Website>
<Address><entry>Ulley Sailing Club</entry>
<entry>Ulley Country Park</entry>
<entry>Pleasley Road</entry>
<entry>Sheffield</entry>
<entry>South Yorkshire</entry>
<entry>S26 3XL</entry>
</Address>
<ContactName><entry>Mark Burkitt, Commodore</entry>
</ContactName>
<Telephone><entry>01709 530287</entry>
<entry>01709 372180</entry>
<entry>Telephone 2 Details:</entry>
<entry>and answerphone, except weekends</entry>
</Telephone>
<Email><entry>commodore@ulleysailingclub.org.uk</entry>
<entry>generalsecretary@ulleysailingclub.org.uk</entry>
</Email>
<ProviderServiceDetails><entry>Sat 10.30am-4.30pm (Apr-Oct), Sun 11am-5pm (Apr-Dec), Wed evenings during the summer months</entry>
</ProviderServiceDetails>
<Provision><ProvisionPlace><entry>Ulley Country Park</entry>
<entry>Pleasley Road (A618)</entry>
<entry>Nr Sheffield</entry>
<entry>South Yorkshire</entry>
<entry>S31 0YL</entry>
</ProvisionPlace>
<ProvisionDaysAndTimes><entry>Saturday, Sunday &amp; Wed evenings, please contact for further details</entry>
</ProvisionDaysAndTimes>
</Provision>
<category><entry>SAILING</entry>
</category>
</SheffieldHYS>
