<SheffieldHYS id="23247">
<BaseURL><entry>http://www.sheffieldhelpyourself.org.uk/full_search_new.asp?group=23247</entry>
</BaseURL>
<HYSID><entry>23247</entry>
</HYSID>
<OrgName><entry>RCCG VICTORY ASSEMBLY</entry>
</OrgName>
<Desc><entry>Part of the Redeemed Christian Church of God which is an international network of Churches.  A multicultural church based in the heart of the city at John street opposite Sheffield United Football Club.  A church with relevant teaching, heartfelt worship, exuberant praise, genuine community and cultural diversity.  Has various group initiatives which reach out to the diverse peoples of the city.  'Revolution' is a students' group which aims to build young adults who make a difference in their community.  A drop-in centre for the homeless and those in need.  'Achievers' which is essentially about building women that pray, act and build others.  Runs a children's church and youth group known as the 'Mighty Ones'.  The Mighty Ones aims to help teenagers deal with the issues surrounding them in their schools and communities while building a deeper relationship with Jesus.  Also hosts a variety of conferences and events during the year including an International Carol service which celebrates Christmas traditions from around the world every December, a worship extravaganza in February 'Psalms Alive' and an annual 'Walking in Victory' conference every October.</entry>
</Desc>
<Website><entry>http://www.victory-assembly.org</entry>
</Website>
<CharityNo><entry>1085107</entry>
</CharityNo>
<Address><entry>Faithcentre</entry>
<entry>99 John Street</entry>
<entry>Sheffield</entry>
<entry>South Yorkshire</entry>
<entry>S2 4QX</entry>
</Address>
<ContactName><entry>Sarah Akpaka</entry>
</ContactName>
<Telephone><entry>0114 270 9633</entry>
<entry>Mobile:</entry>
<entry>07960 127809</entry>
</Telephone>
<Email><entry>church.office@victory-assembly.org</entry>
</Email>
<ProviderServiceDetails><entry>Mon-Fri 10am-5pm (office times); Sun at 9.30am (Victory training Bible study), Sunday Services at 10am, 1st, 3rd &amp; 5th Sun at 6.30pm (special evening service with opportuntiy for  personal prayer and ministry), Fri at 6.30pm (Friday night fellowship)</entry>
</ProviderServiceDetails>
<category><entry>PENTECOSTAL CHURCHES</entry>
</category>
</SheffieldHYS>
