<SheffieldHYS id="23433">
<BaseURL><entry>http://www.sheffieldhelpyourself.org.uk/full_search_new.asp?group=23433</entry>
</BaseURL>
<HYSID><entry>23433</entry>
</HYSID>
<OrgName><entry>CHARIBAGS - REUSABLE BAGS WITH A SOCIAL CONSCIENCE</entry>
</OrgName>
<AltName><entry>CHARIBAND/CHARIBAGS</entry>
</AltName>
<Desc><entry>Chariband is a social enterprise working in partnership with the Children's Hospital Charity (TCHC), the Sheffield Star and BBC Radio Sheffield to create awareness and raise funds for TCHC latest appeal, BBC Kid's Scanner appeal.  In 2006 Chariband launched a bespoke range of reusable bags called charibags as a way to thank the hospital for caring for their son when he had to have a short stay in Intensive Care.  To date the TCHC charibag range have potentially saved nearly 5 million plastic bags from being used in and around Sheffield and have raised over £36,000 for the hospital charity with a percentage also going to city schools and the South Yorkshire Flood Disaster Fund.  This ongoing campaign has challenged people's bad bag habits and encouraged local pride and care for others.  Following this success and the demand for an alternative to plastic bags, Chariband have created bespoke reusable bags for many charities, schools, businesses, not-for-profit and community groups throughout the UK, locally to include St Luke's Hospice, FABLE, The University of Sheffield, Sheffield Hallam University, Neurocare and Barnsley Hospice.  Chariband also run a Remembrance Campaign "Loved today, yesterday and forever more", a range of remembrance pin badges and wristbands that aim to give comfort and strength to those bereaved, to help raise public awareness and promote the service bereavement-related organisations provide.</entry>
</Desc>
<Website><entry>http://www.chariband.co.uk</entry>
</Website>
<Address><entry>Chariband</entry>
<entry>Unit 28</entry>
<entry>SCEDU</entry>
<entry>53 Mowbray Street</entry>
<entry>Sheffield</entry>
<entry>South Yorkshire</entry>
<entry>S3 8EN</entry>
</Address>
<ContactName><entry>Glenda Kirby, Charibag Fundraising Co-ordinator</entry>
</ContactName>
<Telephone><entry>0114 360 9454</entry>
</Telephone>
<Fax><entry>0114 276 6939</entry>
<entry>Mobile:</entry>
<entry>07851 004435</entry>
<entry>Mobile:</entry>
<entry>07749 045685</entry>
</Fax>
<Email><entry>sales@chariband.co.uk</entry>
</Email>
<ProviderServiceDetails><entry>Mon-Fri 9am-6pm</entry>
</ProviderServiceDetails>
<Provision><ProvisionPlace><entry>Various venues and times</entry>
<entry>please contact for details</entry>
</ProvisionPlace>
<ProvisionDaysAndTimes><entry>Please see website for details</entry>
</ProvisionDaysAndTimes>
</Provision>
<category><entry>HEALTH - FUNDRAISING, RESEARCH AND VOLUNTARY SUPPORT</entry>
</category>
</SheffieldHYS>
