<SheffieldHYS id="23545">
<BaseURL><entry>http://www.sheffieldhelpyourself.org.uk/full_search_new.asp?group=23545</entry>
</BaseURL>
<HYSID><entry>23545</entry>
</HYSID>
<OrgName><entry>RECYCLING BRING BANK SITE -  POSTAL DISTRICT 2</entry>
</OrgName>
<Desc><entry>Alderson Road Car Park, Alderson Road - glass, steel cans, aluminium cans.  Anchor Court, 260 St Aidans Drive - glass.  Arbourthorne Public House, 6 Errington Way - glass.  B&amp;Q Warehouse, Queens Road - paper, glass, textiles, plastics, steel cans, aluminium cans, card, shoes.  Charlotte Road Car Park, Charlotte Road - glass, steel cans, aluminium cans.  Co-op Supermarket, 40 Manor Park Centre - paper, glass, textiles.  Earl Marshall Public House, 291 East Bank Road - paper, glass, textiles, plastics, steel cans, aluminium cans, shoes.  Earl Public House, 528 Queens Road - glass.   Heeley City Farm, Richards Road - paper, glass, textiles, plastics, steel cans, aluminium cans, shoes.  Holland Road Car Park, Holland Road - glass, steel cans, aluminium cans.  Manor Lodge Primary School, Manor Lane - paper.  NCHA, Barnes Court, Shrewsbury Road - glass.  NCHA, Edwin close - paper, glass, textiles, plastics, steel cans, aluminium cans, shoes.  Norfolk Park Special School, Park Grange Road - paper.  Salvation Army, Duke Street - textiles.  Sheffield College, Castle North Site, Granville Street - paper, glass, plastics, steel cans, aluminium cans.  Sheffield College, Castle South Site, Granville Street - paper, glass.  Sheffield Trades &amp; Labour Club, Duke Street - glass.  Spires Centre, 600 East Bank Road - glass.  St Elizabeth Close, off Heeley Bank Road - paper, glass.  St Marys Church, Community Centre, Bramall Lane - paper, glass, plastics, steel cans, aluminium cans.   Wybourn Primary School, Manor Oaks Road - plastics, aluminium cans, steel cans, textiles.</entry>
</Desc>
<Website><entry>http://www.veoliaenvironmentalservices.co.uk/sheffield/</entry>
</Website>
<Address><entry>Veolia Environmental Services PLC</entry>
<entry>Lumley Street Service Centre</entry>
<entry>Lumley Street</entry>
<entry>Sheffield</entry>
<entry>South Yorkshire</entry>
<entry>S4 7ZJ</entry>
</Address>
<DisabledAccess><entry>Wheelchair Accessible;</entry>
<entry>Wheelchair Accessible Toilet;</entry>
</DisabledAccess>
<Telephone><entry>0114 273 4567</entry>
<entry>Telephone 1 Details:</entry>
<entry>Main Switchboard</entry>
<entry>0114 228 3630</entry>
<entry>Telephone 2 Details:</entry>
<entry>Office</entry>
</Telephone>
<ProviderServiceDetails><entry>Mon-Fri 9am-5pm</entry>
</ProviderServiceDetails>
<category><entry>RECYCLING FACILITIES</entry>
</category>
</SheffieldHYS>
