<SheffieldHYS id="23551">
<BaseURL><entry>http://www.sheffieldhelpyourself.org.uk/full_search_new.asp?group=23551</entry>
</BaseURL>
<HYSID><entry>23551</entry>
</HYSID>
<OrgName><entry>RECYCLING BRING BANK SITE -  POSTAL DISTRICT 6</entry>
</OrgName>
<Desc><entry>Bradfield Dungworth School, The Green, Dungworth - paper.  Car Park, The Sands, off Fair House Lane, Low Bradfield - paper, glass, textiles, plastics, steel cans, aluminium cans, books, shoes.   Deer Park Flats, Deer Park Road - paper.  Dyke Convenience Store, 199 Dykes Hall Road - textiles.  Foxhill Dry Cleaners, 273 Fox Hill Road - textiles.  Freedom Road Car Park - paper, glass, textiles, plastics, steel cans, aluminium cans, books, shoes.  Hall Park Hill, Stannington - paper, glass, textiles, plastics, steel cans, aluminium cans, shoes.  Hillsborough College, Livesey Street - paper, glass.  Hillsborough Leisure Centre, Penistone Road - textiles, glass.  Loxley Nurseries, Long Lane, off Loxley Road - paper, glass, textiles, plastics, steel cans, aluminium cans.  Loxley Park Residential Home, Loxley Road - glass.  Morrisons, Hillsborough Barracks, 669 Penistone Road - paper, glass, textiles, plastics, steel cans, aluminium cans, books, shoes.  NCHA, Limbrick Close - paper, glass.  Nook Lane School, Nook Lane - paper.  Park &amp; Ride Facility, Middlewood Road - paper, glass.  Parson Cross Primary School, Halifax Road - paper, plastics, steel cans, aluminium cans.  Pond Road Shops, Stannington - paper, textiles.  Rural Lane Car Park, Rural Lane - paper, glass, plastics, steel cans, aluminium cans.  Shipton Street,  Ex Housing Area Office Car Park - paper, glass, textiles.  Stannington Library - Uppergate Road - paper, glass, textiles, plastics, steel cans, aluminium cans, books, card, shoes.  Tesco, Infirmary Road - paper, glass, textiles, plastics, steel cans, aluminium cans, books, card, shoes.  The Sportsman Public House, Oldfield Road - glass, textiles.  Wadsley Bridge Social Club, Halifax Road - glass, textiles, plastics, steel cans, aluminium cans, shoes.  Wadsley Social Club, The Drive - glass.  Walkley Cottage Public House, 46 Bole Hill Road - glass, textiles.   Walkley WMC, 207 Providence Road - paper, glass, textiles, plastics, steel cans, aluminium cans.  Winn Grove, off Winn Gardens - paper, glass, plastics, steel cans, aluminium cans.  Worrall Road News, Worrall Road - textiles.  Yew Tree Public House, Loxley New Road - paper, glass, textiles, plastics, steel cans, aluminium cans.</entry>
</Desc>
<Website><entry>http://www.veoliaenvironmentalservices.co.uk/sheffield/</entry>
</Website>
<Address><entry>Veolia Environmental Services PLC</entry>
<entry>Lumley Street Service Centre</entry>
<entry>Lumley Street</entry>
<entry>Sheffield</entry>
<entry>South Yorkshire</entry>
<entry>S4 7ZJ</entry>
</Address>
<DisabledAccess><entry>Wheelchair Accessible;</entry>
<entry>Wheelchair Accessible Toilet;</entry>
</DisabledAccess>
<Telephone><entry>0114 273 4567</entry>
<entry>Telephone 1 Details:</entry>
<entry>Main Switchboard</entry>
<entry>0114 228 3630</entry>
<entry>Telephone 2 Details:</entry>
<entry>Office</entry>
</Telephone>
<category><entry>RECYCLING FACILITIES</entry>
</category>
</SheffieldHYS>
