<SheffieldHYS id="23572">
<BaseURL><entry>http://www.sheffieldhelpyourself.org.uk/full_search_new.asp?group=23572</entry>
</BaseURL>
<HYSID><entry>23572</entry>
</HYSID>
<OrgName><entry>RECYCLING BRING BANK SITE -  POSTAL DISTRICT 10</entry>
</OrgName>
<Desc><entry>Broomhall Nursery School, 4 Broomhall Road - paper.  Crewe Flats, Brocco Bank/Clarkehouse Road - paper, glass, textiles, plastics, steel cans, aluminium cans.  Endcliffe Crescent Flats, Endcliffe Crescent - paper, glass, textiles, plastics, steel cans, aluminium cans.  Housing Association, Northfield Close - glass, plastics, steel cans, aluminium cans.  Lydgate Junior School, Manchester Road - paper.  NCHA, Ranmoor View - paper, glass, textiles, plastics, steel cans, aluminium cans.  Notre Dame High School, Fulwood Road - paper.  Old Fulwood Road - paper, glass, textiles, plastics, steel cans, aluminium cans.  Scout Hut, Fulwood Road - glass.  Sheffield University, Endcliffe Avenue - glass, plastics, steel cans, aluminium cans.  Springfield Primary School, Broomspring Lane - paper.  St Maries Infant School, Fulwood Road - paper.  Stephenson Hall, Oakholme Road - glass.  Tapton Hall, Crookes Road - paper, glass, books, card.  Tapton Hall, Main Car Park, Taptonville Road - paper, glass, textiles, plastics, steel cans, aluminium cans.  The Punchbowl Public House, Crookes - textiles.  The Sportsman Public House Car Park, Redmires Road - glass, textiles, plastics, steel cans, aluminium cans.  University of Sheffield, Arts Tower, Western Bank - paper, glass, plastics, steel cans, aluminium cans.  Weston Park Hospital, Whitham Road - paper, glass.</entry>
</Desc>
<Website><entry>http://www.veoliaenvironmentalservices.co.uk/sheffield</entry>
</Website>
<Address><entry>Veolia Environmental Services PLC</entry>
<entry>Lumley Street Service Centre</entry>
<entry>Lumley Street</entry>
<entry>Sheffield</entry>
<entry>South Yorkshire</entry>
<entry>S4 7ZJ</entry>
</Address>
<DisabledAccess><entry>Wheelchair Accessible;</entry>
<entry>Wheelchair Accessible Toilet;</entry>
</DisabledAccess>
<Telephone><entry>0114 273 4567</entry>
<entry>Telephone 1 Details:</entry>
<entry>Main Switchboard</entry>
<entry>0114 228 3630</entry>
<entry>Telephone 2 Details:</entry>
<entry>Office</entry>
</Telephone>
<category><entry>RECYCLING FACILITIES</entry>
</category>
</SheffieldHYS>
