<SheffieldHYS id="24746">
<BaseURL><entry>http://www.sheffieldhelpyourself.org.uk/full_search_new.asp?group=24746</entry>
</BaseURL>
<HYSID><entry>24746</entry>
</HYSID>
<OrgName><entry>PRIMARY CARE ADDICTION SERVICE SHEFFIELD (PCASS)</entry>
</OrgName>
<AltName><entry>PRIMARY CARE CLINIC FOR DRUG DEPENDENCY (FORMER NAME)</entry>
</AltName>
<Desc><entry>An NHS service which is commissioned by Sheffield Drug and Alcohol Action Team (DAAT) to provide the GP Shared Care Deputising Service, GP Shared Care Support (Drugs and Alcohol) and Specialist Pregnancy Clinic.  

The GP Shared Care Deputising Service provides community prescribing for drug misuse within a GP-led service assisted by a specialist drug team.  The service provides a range of specialist prescribing interventions including stabilisation on substitute opioids, including dose titration, prescribing for a sustained period to substitute illicit drugs such as methodone and buprenorphine (maintenance prescribing), prescribing for withdrawal from opioids with opioid of non-opioid medications such as buprenorphine and lofexidine (community detoxification), prescribing to prevent relapse, stabilisation and withdrawal from sedatives such as benzodiazepines, prescribing for assisted withdrawal from alcohol where appropriate and treatment for stimulant users which may include symptomatic prescribing and non-medical prescribing (by nurses and pharmacists).  

The service is delivered by a multi-disciplinary substance misuse team, employing GPs, clinical nurse specialists and drug workers.  Works in partnership with Specialist Substance Misuse Midwives at Jessops Hospital, a Substance Misuse Social Worker and other clinical and safeguarding professionals in a multi disciplinary team.  Referral by health professional only.</entry>
</Desc>
<Langs><entry>By arrangement</entry>
</Langs>
<Pubs><entry>Sheffield DAAT Directory</entry>
</Pubs>
<Address><entry>Guernsey House</entry>
<entry>84 Guernsey Road</entry>
<entry>Sheffield</entry>
<entry>South Yorkshire</entry>
<entry>S2 4HG</entry>
</Address>
<DisabledAccess><entry>Wheelchair Accessible;</entry>
</DisabledAccess>
<Telephone><entry>0114 226 1844</entry>
<entry>Telephone 1 Details:</entry>
<entry>Patient Line</entry>
<entry>0114 226 1843</entry>
<entry>Telephone 2 Details:</entry>
<entry>External Agencies Line</entry>
</Telephone>
<Fax><entry>0114 226 1845</entry>
</Fax>
<Email><entry>pcass@sheffieldpct.nhs.uk</entry>
</Email>
<ProviderServiceDetails><entry>Mon, Tues, Thurs &amp; Fri 9am-5pm, Wed 11am-7pm</entry>
</ProviderServiceDetails>
<category><entry>DRUG ABUSE AND REHABILITATION</entry>
</category>
</SheffieldHYS>
