<SheffieldHYS id="24994">
<BaseURL><entry>http://www.sheffieldhelpyourself.org.uk/full_search_new.asp?group=24994</entry>
</BaseURL>
<HYSID><entry>24994</entry>
</HYSID>
<OrgName><entry>ADVICE HELPLINE - SHEFFIELD DOMESTIC ABUSE HELPLINE</entry>
</OrgName>
<Desc><entry>The helpline is a single city wide number for people who are experiencing or recovering from domestic and sexual abuse and need support.  It is also for people worried about family members or friends who want to find out more about services in Sheffield, and professionals who want information to support their clients.  Staffed by specialist voluntary sector workers.  Any matters you discuss with the helpline team are confidential and respect the need for safety.  If there are urgent safety issues for the caller, another adult, child or young person which require the team to disclose information they will try to keep you involved and informed of this as far as possible.  If the team help the caller to access another service they will ask permission to pass on any relevant information.  The helpline service is part of The Sheffield Domestic Abuse Partnership, which is a multi-agency project that brings together specialist workers from domestic and sexual abuse services to keep people safe.  They include voluntary and statutory agencies: Independent Domestic Violence Advocacy Service (IDVAS), a citywide domestic abuse outreach service, social workers, youth offending service and the police.  Calls to the helpline are free from landlines and from the main mobile phone providers.</entry>
</Desc>
<Website><entry>http://www.sheffdap.org.uk</entry>
</Website>
<Langs><entry>Mirpuri, Punjabi, Urdu</entry>
</Langs>
<Address><entry>Please contact for details</entry>
</Address>
<Telephone><entry>0808 808 2241</entry>
<entry>Telephone 1 Details:</entry>
<entry>Helpline - Mon, Tues, Thurs, Fri 10am-4pm, Wed 10am-7pm and answerphone with emergency contact details</entry>
<entry>0114 296 4994</entry>
<entry>Telephone 2 Details:</entry>
<entry>Office Line</entry>
</Telephone>
<Email><entry>help@sheffdap.org.uk</entry>
<entry>info@sheffdap.org.uk</entry>
</Email>
<category><entry>VIOLENCE AND SEXUAL ABUSE</entry>
</category>
</SheffieldHYS>
